<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<contexts>
	<context id="canonicalization" title="XML Canonicalization (remove comments)">
    <description>During canonicalization, the XML document is being normalized. This e.g. includes the removal of unnecessary whitespaces in tags, alphabetic ordering of attributes and UTF-8 as encoding. This variant will remove any XML comment and replace it with empty lines.</description>
	</context>
	<context id="canonicalizationcomments" title="XML Canonicalization (maintain comments)">
    <description>During canonicalization, the XML document is being normalized. This e.g. includes the removal of unnecessary whitespaces in tags, alphabetic ordering of attributes and UTF-8 as encoding. This variant keeps all XML comment.</description>
	</context>
	<context id="signature" title="XML Signature">
    <description>Creates a new XML Signature for the selected XML document. You can sign the complete document or a fragment of it. Three signature variants - &lt;b&gt;enveloping&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;enveloped&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;detached&lt;/b&gt; - are available.</description>
	</context>
	<context id="verification" title="XML Verification">
      <description>During verification, all XML Signatures in the active XML document are verified. The result is displayed in the <b>XML Signatures</b> view.</description>
	</context>
	<context id="encryption" title="XML Encryption">
    <description>Creates a new XML Encryption for the selected XML document. You can encrypt the complete XML document or a fragment.</description>
	</context>
    <context id="decryption" title="XML Decryption">
       <description>Decrypts a chosen encryption in the active XML document and restores its plaintext.</description>
    </context>
	<context id="wizard_signature_resource">
		<description>Select a &lt;b&gt;resource&lt;/b&gt; to sign (the complete document or a fragment of it), the &lt;b&gt;signature type&lt;/b&gt; (enveloping, enveloped or detached) and a &lt;b&gt;key option&lt;/b&gt; (create a new one or use an existing one). The &lt;b&gt;Basic Security Profile&lt;/b&gt; option increases interoperability of Web Service Security.</description>
		<topic href="html/signature/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="html/signature/page_resource.html" label="Resource and Signature Type"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_signature_open_key">
		<description>Provide all required information for the &lt;b&gt;key to use&lt;/b&gt; in the current signing process.</description>
		<topic href="html/signature/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="html/signature/page_open_key.html" label="Open a key"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_signature_create_key">
		<description>Provide all required information to &lt;b&gt;insert a new key&lt;/b&gt; into a keystore. This key will be used in the current signing process and is stored in the selected keystore.</description>
		<topic href="html/signature/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="html/signature/page_create_key.html" label="Create a key"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_signature_create_keystore">
		<description>Provide all required information to &lt;b&gt;create a new keystore&lt;/b&gt; together with &lt;b&gt;a new key&lt;/b&gt;. This key will be used in the current signing process and is stored in the current project folder as [Keystore Name].jks.</description>
		<topic href="html/signature/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="html/signature/page_create_keystore.html" label="Create a keystore and key"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_signature_algorithms">
		<description>Select a &lt;b&gt;canonicalization and a transformation algorithm&lt;/b&gt;, a &lt;b&gt;message digest and a signature algorithm&lt;/b&gt;. The &lt;b&gt;signature properties&lt;/b&gt; are optional. A new property can be added by clicking on the + button. The &lt;b&gt;signature id&lt;/b&gt; is optional but makes it much easier to identify the signature. The characters &lt;, &gt;, &amp;, &quot;, &apos; and blanks are not allowed as id (signature id and signature property id), the maximum length is 20 characters. Selecting the &lt;b&gt;Start Encryption Wizard afterwards&lt;/b&gt; checkbox opens the Encryption Wizard after a successful digital signature operation.</description>
		<topic href="html/signature/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="html/signature/page_algorithms.html" label="Algorithms and Signature Properties"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_encryption_resource" title="Resource and Encryption Type">
		<description>Select the &lt;b&gt;resource&lt;/b&gt; to encrypt (the complete document or a fragment of it), the &lt;b&gt;encryption type&lt;/b&gt; (enveloping or detached) and a &lt;b&gt;key option&lt;/b&gt; (use an existing one, insert a new key in a keystore, create a new keystore and a new key). The &lt;b&gt;Basic Security Profile&lt;/b&gt; option increases interoperability of Web Service Security.</description>
		<topic href="html/encryption/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
		<topic href="html/encryption/page_resource.html" label="Resource and Encryption Type"/>
	</context>
    <context id="wizard_encryption_open_key" title="Use a key from an existing keystore">
        <description>Use an existing key in the active encryption process. Provide all required information for this key and continue to the last wizard page.</description>
        <topic href="html/encryption/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
        <topic href="html/encryption/page_open_key.html" label="Use a key from an existing keystore"/>
    </context>
    <context id="wizard_encryption_create_key" title="Insert a new key in an existing keystore">
        <description>Create a new key for the active encryption process. Provide all required information and insert the new key into an existing keystore and continue to the last wizard page.</description>
        <topic href="html/encryption/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
        <topic href="html/encryption/page_create_key.html" label="Insert a new key in an existing keystore"/>
    </context>
    <context id="wizard_encryption_create_keystore" title="Create a new key and a new keystore">
        <description>Create a new keystore and insert a new key to use in the active encryption process. Provide all required information and continue to the last wizard page.&lt;br&gt;
The keystore will be stored in the current (project) folder as [Keystore Name].jks.</description>
        <topic href="html/encryption/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
        <topic href="html/encryption/page_create_keystore.html" label="Create a new key and a new keystore"/>
    </context>
	<context id="wizard_encryption_algorithms" title="Algorithms and Encryption Properties">
		<description>Select the &lt;b&gt;encryption algorithms&lt;/b&gt; and decide whether you want to completely encrypt the XML data or keep the root element as plain text. The &lt;b&gt;encryption id&lt;/b&gt; is optional but makes it much easier to identify the encryption. The characters &lt;, &gt;, &amp;, &quot;, &apos; and blanks are not allowed as id, the maximum length is 20 characters. Selecting the &lt;b&gt;Start Digital Signature Wizard afterwards&lt;/b&gt; checkbox opens the &lt;b&gt;XML Signature Wizard&lt;/b&gt; after a successful encryption operation.</description>
		<topic href="html/encryption/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
		<topic href="html/encryption/page_algorithms.html" label="Algorithms and Encryption Properties"/>
	</context>
	<context id="xpath_dialog">
		<description>This dialog displays all XML elements in the active XML document as unique XPath expressions. You can select exactly one element you want to use in the current signing or encrypting process.</description>
		<topic href="html/signature/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="html/encryption/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_decryption_resource" title="Encryption Type and ID">
		<description>If you didn&apos;t enter an &lt;b&gt;encryption id&lt;/b&gt; during the encryption process you can only select to decrypt the first encrypted data found in the selected document. Otherwise select the desired encryption id.

Select the encryption type (enveloping or detached). Selecting detached starts to search the selected encryption (identified by the id) for the reference to the detached file. This URI information is displayed below.

Click &lt;b&gt;Next&lt;/b&gt; to continue to the next wizard page.</description>
		<topic href="html/decryption/decrypt.html" label="XML Decryption Wizard"/>
		<topic href="html/decryption/page_resource.html" label="Resource"/>
	</context>
    <context id="wizard_decryption_keystore" title="Encryption Keystore and Key">
       <description>Select the &lt;b&gt;Keystore&lt;/b&gt; used for encrypting this document (-fragment) and enter the &lt;b&gt;password&lt;/b&gt; for the store. Provide the &lt;b&gt;key name&lt;/b&gt; and enter the corresponding &lt;b&gt;password&lt;/b&gt;. Click &lt;b&gt;Next&lt;/b&gt; to start the decryption process.</description>
       <topic href="html/decryption/decrypt.html" label="XML Decryption Wizard"/>
       <topic href="html/decryption/page_open_a_key.html" label="Open a key"/>
    </context>
	<context id="preferences_general">
		<description>This preference page allows you to configure the general preferences of the &lt;b&gt;XML Security Tools&lt;/b&gt; including &lt;b&gt;Canonicalization&lt;/b&gt; settings.</description>
		<topic href="html/canonicalization/canonicalize.html" label="Canonicalization"/>
		<topic href="html/preferences/general.html" label="XML Security Tools Preferences"/>
	</context>
	<context id="preferences_signature">
		<description>This preference page allows you to configure the preferences for the &lt;b&gt;Quick Signature&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Quick Verification&lt;/b&gt; functionality of the &lt;b&gt;XML Security Tools&lt;/b&gt;.</description>
		<topic href="html/quickfunctions/quickfunctions.html" label="Quick Signature"/>
		<topic href="html/preferences/signature.html" label="Quick Signature Preferences"/>
	</context>
	<context id="preferences_encryption">
		<description>This preference page allows you to configure the preferences for the &lt;b&gt;Quick Encryption&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Quick Decryption&lt;/b&gt; functionality of the &lt;b&gt;XML Security Tools&lt;/b&gt;.</description>
		<topic href="html/quickfunctions/quickfunctions.html" label="Quick Encryption"/>
		<topic href="html/preferences/encryption.html" label="Quick Encryption Preferences"/>
	</context>
    <context id="signature_view">
        <description>This view displays all &lt;b&gt;XML Signatures&lt;/b&gt; (valid, invalid and unkown) found in the selected XML document. Click &lt;b&gt;Refresh&lt;/b&gt; for a new scan of the active XML document. Select one verification result and click &lt;b&gt;Properties&lt;/b&gt; for detailed information about the selected XML Signature.</description>
        <topic href="html/verification/verify.html" label="XML Signatures View"/>
    </context>
</contexts>
