<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="XML Signature">
   <intro href="/org.jcryptool.crypto.xml.help/nl/de/help/signature/sign.html">
      <description>
         Welcome to the <b>XML Signature</b> tutorial for the <b>JCrypTool XML Security</b> implementation.<br/>
This tutorial will show you step by step how to sign an arbitrary XML document using the <b>XML Signature Wizard</b>.<br/>
You will need an XML document to sign. To start this tutorial click the <b>Click to Begin</b> button below.<br/>
By the way, this tutorial shows only some possibilities of the XML Signature Wizard. You can find more information in the extensive online help.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Resource and Signature Type" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/org.jcryptool.crypto.xml.help/nl/de/help/signature/page_resource.html">
      <description>
         Now it&apos;s time to actually sign your XML document. Start the <b>XML Signature Wizard</b> by clicking on <b>New Signature...</b> in the <b>XML Security</b> section in the <b>Algorithm Explorer</b>. The wizard consists of three pages.<br/>
On the first page you have to select the resource you want to sign (the complete document, a text selection or a node defined by an XPath expression). In order to sign a text selection you must select a well-formed part of your XML document before you start the wizard.<br/>
After that you have to select which signature type you want to use (enveloping, enveloped or detached).rmation to create a new one.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Key" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/org.jcryptool.crypto.xml.help/nl/de/help/signature/page_key.html">
      <description>
         You must use an existing key in the JCrypTool keystore and continue the signature process with it.      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Algorithms and Signature Properties" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/org.jcryptool.crypto.xml.help/nl/de/help/signature/page_algorithms.html">
      <description>
         The last page of the XML Signature Wizard requires the algorithms selections for the signature as well as the canonicalization and transformation algorithms. You must select an algorithm in every field.<br/>
You can only use RSA algorithms with a RSA keystore and DSA algorithms with a DSA keystore.<br/>
The Signature Properties are optional and can extend a signature with arbitrary information.<br/>
At last you can enter an id to identify your signature (strongly recommended for verification).<br/>
By selecting the &apos;Start Encryption Wizard afterwards&apos; checkbox the XML Encryption Wizard will be called after the signature is created.<br/>
After providing all required information you can sign the document by clicking on the &apos;Finish&apos; button.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
