<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<contexts>
   <context id="algorithmsPreferences" title="Algorithms">
      <description>This is the start page for crypto plug-ins belonging to the category <b>Algorithms</b>. The subpages here do contain the settings for plug-ins available in this category. Not every crypto plug-in does provide its own preferences.</description>
      <topic href="../org.jcryptool.core.help/$nl$/help/users/algorithms/toc.html" label="Algorithms"/>
   </context>
   <context id="analysisPreferences" title="Analysis">
      <description>This is the start page for crypto plug-ins belonging to the category <b>Analysis</b>. The subpages here do contain the settings for plug-ins available in this category. Not every crypto plug-in does provide its own preferences.</description>
      <topic href="../org.jcryptool.core.help/$nl$/help/users/analysis/toc.html" label="Analysis"/>
   </context>
   <context id="cryptoPreferences" title="Cryptography">
      <description>This is the general category for cryptographic settings of all kind. The subpages contain general settings for different crypto plug-ins. e.g. classical alphabets and the keystores for modern algorithms can be configured in this category. Normally those settings are used in more than one plug-in.</description>
      <topic href="../org.jcryptool.core.help/$nl$/help/users/general/preferences_provider.html" label="Crypto Provider"/>
   </context>
   <context id="editorsPreferences" title="Editors">
      <description>This is the start page for the <b>Editors</b> available in JCrypTool. Subpages do contain specific preferences for every editor (if available).</description>
      <topic href="../org.jcryptool.core.help/$nl$/help/users/general/editors.html" label="Editors"/>
   </context>
   <context id="gamesPreferences" title="Games">
      <description>This is the start page for crypto plug-ins belonging to the category <b>Games</b>. The subpages here do contain the settings for plug-ins available in this category. Not every crypto plug-in does provide its own preferences.</description>
      <topic href="../org.jcryptool.core.help/$nl$/help/users/games/toc.html" label="Games"/>
   </context>
   <context id="visualsPreferences" title="Visualizations">
      <description>This is the start page for crypto plug-ins belonging to the <b>Visualizations</b>. The subpages here do contain the settings for plug-ins available in this category. Not every crypto plug-in does provide its own preferences.</description>
      <topic href="../org.jcryptool.core.help/$nl$/help/users/visualizations/toc.html" label="Visualizations"/>
   </context>
   <context id="generalPreferences" title="General">
      <description>
         This page lets you choose general JCrypTool settings as well as the JCrypTool language. The language is automatically based on the regional settings of your operating system, but can be changed here. You have to restart JCrypTool after switching to another language.&lt;br&gt;Be aware that not all plug-ins (dialogs, help, ...) may be available in the selected language. This page lets you choose general JCrypTool settings as well as the JCrypTool language. The language is automatically based on the regional settings of your operating system, but can be changed here. You have to restart JCrypTool after switching to another language.</description>
      <topic href="../org.jcryptool.core.help/$nl$/help/users/about/tips.html" label="Tips and Tricks"/>
   </context>
</contexts>
