<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="XML Decryption">
   <intro href="/org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.doc/html/decryption/decrypt.html">
      <description>
         Welcome to the <b>XML Decryption</b> tutorial for the <b>XML Security Tools</b>.<br/>
This tutorial will show you step by step how to decrypt an arbitrary XML document using the <b>XML Decryption Wizard</b>.<br/>
To start this tutorial click the <b>Click to Begin</b> button below. You need an encrypted XML document to proceed.<br/>
By the way, this tutorial shows only some possibilities of the XML Decryption Wizard. You can find more information in the extensive online help.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Open an encrypted XML document" skip="true" href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/tasks/tasks-46.htm">
      <description>
         Open an encrypted XML document (you may have created with the <b>XML Encryption Wizard</b>). You can skip this item if your encrypted XML document is already opened in an editor.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Decrypt the document" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.doc/html/decryption/page_resource.html">
      <description>
         Now it&apos;s time to actually decrypt your XML document. Start the <b>XML Decryption Wizard</b> by clicking on <b>New Decryption...</b> in the context menu <b>XML Security</b>. The wizard consists of one page.<br/>
On this page you have to select the keystore containing the used key (you may have created this keystore in the <b>XML Encryption Wizard</b>) and enter the used key. Both, keystore and key, may require a password which you have to enter as well. After that you can select an encryption ID in the <b>Encryption ID</b> drop down box. In case there are no encryption IDs contained in the XML document you can only select to encrypt the first discovered encryption in the document.<br/>
Your XML document will be decrypted after clicking on <b>Finish</b>. If not you may have entered some incorrect information in the wizard. In this case launch the wizard again and enter the correct information.
	  </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
