<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="XML Signature">
   <intro href="/org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.doc/html/signature/sign.html">
      <description>
         Welcome to the <b>XML Signature</b> tutorial for the <b>XML Security Tools</b>.<br/>
This tutorial will show you step by step how to sign an arbitrary XML document using the <b>XML Signature Wizard</b>.<br/>
You will create a project and an XML document to sign To start this tutorial click the <b>Click to Begin</b> button below. You can skip the first step if you already have a project and an opened XML document.<br/>
By the way, this tutorial shows only some possibilities of the XML Signature Wizard. You can find more information in the extensive online help.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Create a new project and sample document" dialog="true" skip="true" href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/tasks/tasks-42.htm">
      <description>
         The first step is to create a new project (your XML documents must be part of a project to work properly with the XML Security Tools). It doesn&apos;t matter what type of project, the best type is of course an XML project. After that create a new XML document with arbitrary elements, attributes and everything you want to encrypt.<br/>
It is advisable to start with a small XML document and to extend it step by step. You can create a sample project and a sample XML document automatically by clicking on the <b>Click to perform</b> link below. You can skip this step (<b>Click to skip</b> link) if you already have a project and a contained XML document.
      </description>
      <action class="org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.ui.cheatsheets.CreateSampleProject" pluginId="org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.ui" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Resource and Signature Type" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.doc/html/signature/page_resource.html">
      <description>
         Now it&apos;s time to actually sign your XML document. Start the <b>XML Signature Wizard</b> by clicking on <b>New Signature...</b> in the context menu <b>XML Security</b>. The wizard consists of three pages.<br/>
On the first page you have to select the resource you want to sign (the complete document, a text selection or a node defined by an XPath expression). In order to sign a text selection you must select a well-formed part of your XML document before you start the wizard.<br/>
After that you have to select which signature type you want to use (enveloping, enveloped or detached).<br/>
Finally choose a keystore and key option: The wizard enables you to use an existing key, create a new one or even create a new keystore together with a new key. The following wizard page depends on your selection here and will either require to select a keystore/ key or to enter the necessary information to create a new one.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Keystore and Key" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.doc/html/signature/page_keys.html">
      <description>
         You can use an existing key in a Java Keystore (*.jks) and continue the signature process with it. To create a new key enter all data, select a key type and click the <b>Generate</b> button.<br/>
In future signing sessions you can reuse this keystore and key and must only enter the keystore and key passwords. A newly generated keystore is stored in the current project folder and any new key will be used in the active signature process.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Algorithms and Signature Properties" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.doc/html/signature/page_algorithms.html">
      <description>
         The last page of the XML Signature Wizard requires the algorithms selections for the signature as well as the canonicalization and transformation algorithms. You must select an algorithm in every field.<br/>
You can only use RSA algorithms with a RSA keystore and DSA algorithms with a DSA keystore.<br/>
The Signature Properties are optional and can extend a signature with arbitrary information.<br/>
At last you can enter an id to identify your signature (strongly recommended for verification).<br/>
By selecting the &apos;Start Encryption Wizard afterwards&apos; checkbox the XML Encryption Wizard will be called after the signature is created.<br/>
After providing all required information you can sign the document by clicking on the &apos;Finish&apos; button.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
